<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[SachinJot]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[SachinJot]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/sachinjot/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 15:57:52 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/sachinjot/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fashion Shoot ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Fashion Shoot </h1><p>We went to Nashik,Maharashtra for a fashion shoot..when we arrived to my surprise was a beautiful horse farm was there for us to shoot the model for a brand called Cute and curls.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/ff5c1ff808751276a4785c27f2483a443c59ced6.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/sachinjot/fashion-shoot/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1846d089-ee88-4e19-bffe-5f16232356e7</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 15:57:10 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Euro Trip]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Euro Trip</h1><p>Euro Trip for a wedding shoot.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/43049950514923f22dadb8eb56c5f3683b2da0e0.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/sachinjot/euro-trip/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4b4023d7-0d74-4d33-a2a6-a392bbc3d5e6</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 08:56:57 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Film Shoot in Ladakh - Work]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Film Shoot in Ladakh - Work</h1><p>Return Journey was a beautiful experience in its own self as this was my first independent film as a DOP and its a very small crew film with lot of ambitions and aspirations towards filmmaking.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/66bcfb6609ff6fccdacd0e6c0c4b5e6560111ac5.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/sachinjot/advert-shoot-in-surat-work/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c80429e2-eb5f-4de9-9f1b-8072d63c75c3</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2016 04:21:37 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bookings]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Bookings</h1><p>Cinematographer/Editor and a filmmaker I am a passionate artist who loves to travel...loves colors,food and roadtrips.I am working towards making a difference through my work.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/ff1700fd392f72d2fb07937116a8e2181d8c0f64.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/sachinjot/bookings/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e6168d2b-0942-4c8c-8bdd-22da644ae99d</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 08:01:31 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[About Me]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>About Me</h1><p>Sachin Jot is a Cinematographer and a Film-maker with an appreciable amount of experience with documentary films, short films and feature films. His filmography includes notable accomplishments, where he assisted the chief DOP (Director of Photography) Sampan Narula for the movie Kamasutra 3D as a special unit DOP. He worked as the chief DOP for a Cannes Film Festival entry called 'Monologues of an Indian Sex Maniac' directed by Shreetama Dutta. He also shot and directed the short film 'Do Not Smoke', which was selected for Nashik International Film Festival. Rainy Days and Border Line are other short films where he was the chief DOP. Sachin Jot is also an experienced film editor. Live My Life, Not The Film!, Neron and Chandni Raat (Music Video) being a few of his undertakings as an editor.



     Sachin Jot is the chief Director of Photography for Return Journey. The film is shot at various locations with picturesque beauty and aesthetic appeal, and Mr. Jot has successfully managed to capture their essence, owing to his experienced skill set. The locations brings to its audience a diverse spectrum of visuals, be it the vastness of the Arabian Sea, the shining White Desert of the Rann of Kutch, the Golden sand of Thar Desert in contrast to the clear blue skies, the green surroundings of the Lahaul valley and the mighty mountains of the Ladakh ranges or the monuments, forts and monasteries spread across the route. The indoor scenes are also shot with a similarly effective technique and the results are equally noteworthy.
</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/4c5b3b5757f159abc4e57076879fa64fe12f4a1c.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/sachinjot/about-me/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">08024d58-f7fa-4f91-9286-87d7ac4574f1</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2016 04:22:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>